Good evening, this is Hiragana.
Today, I would like to introduce KEDOIN's office and TRILION's office.
As you can see, the office looks like this.
It's really nice, isn't it?
The ideal room is a little dark.
Well, it's always like this,
I wonder if there's anything to see here.
Harukun and
Rin and Guku sitting here, and Bakai-san sitting over here.
Here, can you see it? Here, you see? Here, for the first time, he's sitting here.
It's like he's sitting here for the first time.
I like this sofa.
This one here.
It costs about 500,000 yen.
Expensive, isn't it?
May I sit in your chair?
Like this, if you'll excuse me.
But, Mr. Baker, put your feet up here like this.
I'm too modest to do it.
It turns!
What a stylish item!
Where do you find these things, Mr. Biz?
And the big rope clock!
I like interior design.
Why is that?
There's a lot of stuff around here.
All the things I want.
It's all here.
This wood, what is it?
What's it for? This wood.What do you use it for? This tree.
Mr. Kedlin, I think he used to hang hats and stuff on it.
I want this tree.
Oh! You turned on the light.
Thank you, Narii.
What is this?
I've only seen them on pirate ships.
I'm sorry, but I have to warn you.
A chameleon? What is this?
It's like a chameleon from the Warriors of the North.
Is this video okay?
Is there a reason for this? Here.
Oh, this.
This is the drink you've been drinking.
It's oolong tea.
Just putting it in this bottle makes it look classy.
I drink highballs sometimes, too.
I thought I'd put it in this.
Wow!
This is amazing!
Wow! This is fun!
I play with this a lot.
There's a scene where they're all watching TV here.
It's amazing.
You know, the food sets, they're all fake, but they're not real.
It's not real.
It's real.
And this... when you get out of here, there's a hallway... like this.
I didn't know it was there.I didn't know this was there.
Kedwin Event Capital Kedwin's office is there, and when you go like this...
It's set up right here.
And if I walk like this, I'll be heading this way.
It's right next to here.
Trillion Games.
Trillionaire's office is right here.
Well...
Everything was empty, this set was already finished.
But for this YouTube video, everyone has restored it.
The art department...
The art department did all the work, including the hair-doctor's office.
They did everything for us.
It's amazing, isn't it?
There was a lot of interesting stuff at the Crunchy Lab.
I'm sorry I couldn't take pictures of them.
I don't know if you have any pictures.
They wrote things like "tea rice" and "milk.
You guys were so playful.
It's interesting to see their names and quotes.
Here's our new character, Trilliman.
Mirnyan and...
T-B-Co.
That's right.
I just shot a scene where I put these on and said, "Here we go.
I made all these TVs and everything... and they're all labeled "Lileks Special Delivery.
Do you want to see?
I made everything like this.
This is amazing.
Amazing, isn't it?Amazing, isn't it?
So, here it is.
I'm sure many of you have noticed.
This tissue.
Me and Mr. Meglo...
We have the same tissue case.
Maybe it's just a coincidence.
He put it here.
This is the chair I sit on during breaks.
Meguro, me, Rinrin and Sakura...
Sakura-san and many others.
I want to show it to you. Will you sell me some? I'd like to have some.
I'd like to buy one... Prilimantes TV and Mirnyan... this is amazing!
I'm afraid of breaking it! I tend to break things like this!
Handmade paper mache? Wow!
Wow! What's this?
It's handmade. The hat and everything looks like paper mache.
Eyes and mouth are taped on too. I'm afraid of breaking it!
And then...
Some kind of refrigerator.
This refrigerator.
Haru-kun dropped a bunch of cream puffs in it.
Oh, wow.
It's full of stuff.
Wait!
The macarons Jin and I brought you are still here.
I wonder if I can eat them.
This conference room is great.
I love it. I love it.
I love them. They're so uplifting. I think I'll get to work early.I love it. It's so exciting. I can't wait to get back to work.
The lights are like this again. What's this?
What kind of space is this? It's like a speaker or something.
What kind of sound are these speakers? They're real.
You're real too? This is a whiteboard.
Did I spell that right?
And then the main part...
Mr. Kuniyoshi...
Like this.
I like it.
It's fashionable, like beige.
I'd love to have this in my house, too.
I'd love to install this in my house.
Actually, it looks like this.
This black panel is the LED panel.
It's actually a set like this.
This is very rare.
Look.
The back of this trillion-dollar car is a set like this.
I've never seen this before.
It's a forehead desk.
This is the desk with the forehead.
This is where I hacked into
I hacked into the dragon bank.
I'm sorry.
I think I know what this is... if anyone noticed.
It's from the old forehead room.
Rinri and I were talking about it, and we were wondering what it was.
It looks like a mouse. Ears, eyes, nose, and a mouse.
It's probably the first one the forehead ever made.It's probably the first one I ever made with a forehead, which means I'll always have it with me.
I'm thinking about the backbone of it. I love this notepad.
See what it says?
Like this one...
They all have names on them.
Really?
I write lines like this.
You write these lines.
If you're practicing...
What's that? I'm like, "What was that?
I try to remember them here.
If I have a lot of lines...
It's easier to remember if you write it down.
I'm just checking.
I don't actually look at it.
I don't do it by looking at it.
But I do check it.
Hal's desk
There's nothing on Haru's desk.
I've never seen you sitting here working.
This light... this is very expensive...
590,000 yen
The staff said it's 590,000 yen.
I thought I'd like it, but I still have to work harder.
I can't buy it. It looks like this from the outside.
It always looks like this.
I'm always looking at the night view and saying, "Let's do our best here, teaming up with Haru-kun and Kakao, etc.
Facing this LED light.
This is her seat. There's a lot of stuff in her seat.
This is her seat.That's Ling Ling's seat.
I've been writing this Ling Ling Ling, all kinds of niyas.
He's writing this with this as a motif.
This is Ling Ling Ling.
I wonder if she's watching.
I wrote this.
So this is how they practice writing lines in their heads.
There are a lot of long lines.
We practice hard during breaks.
Write it down. This way.
This is...
When Linlin had to wait for a while, she tried to make that tool at this desk.
When he tried to make that tool on this desk... it turned into a box.
This was adopted. It's on the set.
It's in the set.
I actually bought this book, Marketing from Failure.
I'm curious.
I found it on a plate.
I don't know when this is going to be up right now, but...
We're shooting episode 8 and 9 right now.
We're getting close to the end.
It's sad.
This is one of our favorite spaces.
We're shooting episodes 8 and 9 right now.
We haven't finished episode 10 yet.
I don't even know what it's going to be about.
We're going to start shooting episode 9 the day after tomorrow.
We're about to crank it up.
I've been talking with Negoro every day.
It's been a lot of work.It's not easy.
We've been encouraging each other day in and day out.
We've been encouraging each other to do our best every day, but now that it's over, I feel a little sad.
I feel a little sad.
I think it will be over in a few more weeks.
I'd like to run through it.
I've had a life-changing encounter this time.
I want to do my best to be just like you.
I really want to do my best so that I can be just like you.
It was a really good scene with the staff. We were laughing all the time.
I'm sure it's because of the personality of the chairman.
Well, it's not over yet, so we have a lot of hard work to do tomorrow.
We have a lot of things to do.
I introduce the set for this show. I do a lot of set introductions every time I go to a site like this.
I don't know if any of you have watched this far, but please subscribe to my channel.
That's all.
Hiragana
Please watch, promote and share Trillion Games!
Bye bye!
Bye-bye!